Easy to use directional stick
Facts.
Thank you for watching!
yeah yeah yeah, run run run run run run run run run run run run run
yeah yes youtube shooting day yay
I've got a little something for you today.
This is not cute... everyone compliments me on this kind of thing.
I'm sure there was no project for the three of us today, but here's one who was there.
I'm going back to the school now, and I'm going to take a break now.
Ladies and gentlemen...
I think it's Boober.
Boo-boo!
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
Go, q
neat.
We're filming over here now.
I'm filming a 30-minute video of me trying to learn it.
I saw this video.
Round 1
The first half.
Look at this.
Isn't it funny?
He's slipping.
I just wanted to say thank you.
Yooka's sisters.
When they saw you do it, they laughed so hard.
They laugh so hard.
They make fun of me.
You know what, Yooka...
You're not very feminine, are you?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
She said something really bad about me.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
It's more like girl-round-neutral.
I just folded it right there.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
That was bad.
Oh, my God!
You guys need to learn that.
Really...
There are people who can do better.
Including me.
You really do look like me.
Oh, man.
That one day...
You took it, right?
That whole day.
We filmed for a whole day.
I was tired when I was doing it, to be honest.
Yeah, I was tired.
I was like, "I'm done.
I really thought I was.
And so that video...
I wonder how it's going to turn out.
I was like...
But when I saw the finished product.
I'm glad it looks so fun.
I don't know.
We always shoot in a studio.
It's interesting how the background keeps changing.
I thought it would be more fun than usual.
I thought so.
You know...
Claire's...
Yooka's Helmet Story
I don't know if you told me...
Yooka talked like that.
All this time...
She was talking to herself.
I don't know...
He's filming something.
I don't know.
Don't I look good? He's like...
He's talking all by himself.
I thought he was a bad guy... in a way.
Look at this.
Isn't she the opposite? I thought.
I checked with everyone.
I said, "No, she's against it.
I started filming.
You know, even now, when I posted that story...
I got a bunch of DMs saying how cute I was.
Oh, yeah.
What are you doing next month?
I think we have to dance.
I'm going to work at mam's.
Oh...
You mean a new song? No.
What? You haven't made any progress?
How many months do you think we've put this off?
These guys are working on the dance project.
Do you guys remember the dance project in the comments section? Let's write about it in every video.
Let's write about it in every video!
2killa8k
They kept saying that.
But you know what, they didn't even read it.
Oh, ho, ho, ho
One of the reasons for the lack of progress
Ryouchin made a plan for the project.
How are you doing?
Are you crazy?
Maybe not.
It's definitely not the back side of YouTube anymore.
The back side, the back side.
He's really filming the conversation that's going on behind the scenes there.
Is he still doing that?
I'm still working on it.
It's hard to get in.
You want me to film it?
I'm not filming it yet.
A little something.
Something a little bit.
I don't know if I should just go right to the top.
I'll take an image sheet... and take a picture of the backside.
Now it's time for the costume photo shoot, Yuzu.
Today's cute, isn't it?
It's snowing today, isn't it?
It's snowing today, isn't it? It's snowing today.
It's snowing today.
No, it snowed yesterday. I'm adjusting the angle.
I don't know where this picture's going to go, but you're going to want to see it.
Bye-bye. Thank you.
Hey everybody, Toa here.
I'm in the middle of a break.
I'd like to show you my outfit.
I just wanted you to notice...
It's so heavy.
Here's my costume.
The costumes are always different from the chef's.
I like to keep it fresh.
Yes, I'm looking for the perfect date.
The four of them...
They're filming now.
I'm sorry, I've been caught.
Good luck with that.
I think they can hear me.
I think they're doing their best.
Bye-bye.
What are you doing now?
Right now I'm waiting on YouTube.
Yay.
What did you shoot today? Minami.
Well, I took a few of my own.
Oh, we took a picture together.
What did you enjoy?
What was fun?
Misaki's Alive.
You know, I may have asked you something you didn't know.
I'd like to say something to you.
Do your own behind-the-scenes video.
Oh, I see.
Shall I film it myself?
Oh, I think I'll be fine.
That's the way to do it.
That's good.
She said it's fine.
What's up, Momochan?
I'm, uh, on an ideal date.
Oh.
Really.
What was it like?
Oh, my God.
It wasn't even, uh, a play date.
What?
There was a weird vibe.
A five-year-old.
He's got this weird air about him.
With their characteristic goofiness.
It's a weird vibe, isn't it?
I'm trying to be serious, but he's laughing.
I'm trying to be serious, but they're laughing at me.
It's true.
Don't you want to see it today?
You don't have to.
It was so funny.
We worked so hard on it before we did it.
Like this, like that.
That's right.
It was too funny and too subtle.
It's going to be around for a while.
Please take a look.
This is Misaki backstage.
Yay!
Kira and Yuzu are in front of me!
Here we go!
Today's lunch is udon noodles!
The same.
We're together, aren't we?
All together!
When we shoot for YouTube, we often ask you to prepare udon for us.
Bon appétit!
Yum!
It's delicious.
Can I do what I wanted to do today in my spare time?
Yeah. - Okay.
I'm gonna take some pictures from my digital camera and send them to you guys.
Oh, you mean like that? When was it taken?
The music video.
Ohhh...
That's right.
Oh my God!
I want to send it to you guys for the music video, but I'm filming with this right now.
Impossible!
This is from My Daddy, Puppy.
Oh, yeah?
Yes, he gave it to me, or rather, he gave it to me as a hand-me-down, but I didn't buy it.
Shall I show you some of the delicious pictures I took with this digital camera?
Yes, that's why.
I went out for omu-rice with Minami.
Wow, that's really good!
Yes, this is it.
Ta-da!
Isn't this over there? Yes, that's the place!
That's the place I really want to go.
It was so delicious! If you open this, it looks like this.
Surprisingly, Minami and I don't have dinner together that often.
But we had a free time, so we ate together. It was totally delicious!
Come here, Momochan!
High tones.
It's a little different.
It looks much more yellow!
Today, too. It looks yellow when I look at it alone.
How are you today?
I think we talked a lot today.
I'm going to do my best so that you can see it on the Galgal Channel in various places.
I'll do my best to make a statement.
Yes, that's right.
I'll take a picture of this.
Digital cameras are cute, aren't they?
What do you think?
I can't show you.
I'll show you. I'll show you.
Is it back there?
Oh, my God. Okay.
You know, the screen...
Yuuchan... your fingerprints are all over it.
It's a little haunted.
I'm lying. I thought I got a pretty good shot.
What's with the fingerprints?
Wipe the screen once.
Oh, it's clean!
It's good, but it's out of focus.
I may have a long way to go before I'm any good with a camera.
I'm going to seal it once and for all.
Okay, so I'll keep shooting after this.
Good night.
me
Neck rosore
here
Yes, yes!
Yes, OK.
Thank you very much.
Why are you running the video?
It's backstage, isn't it?
If it's a back frame, why is today's video running?
Thank you for watching.
Is that it?
Did you guys get the back frame?
Just a few?
Thank you very much.
Please subscribe to our channel.
Please leave a comment and click the "Good" button.
Bye bye.
This time I am wearing D-Holic's costume.